《欲奴》前情提要
Previously on "Submission..."
我只會住幾個月
I'll only be here for a few months.
你又不能回到那段糟糕的戀情中了
It's not like you can go back to that shitty relationship.
我裝了一整年
I faked it for an entire year.
你正處在一種濫用權力的情況中
You're in a situation where there's an abuse of power.
她簡直目不轉睛
She couldn't take her eyes off of us.
我的上帝  就是她
Oh, my God. That's her.
-這是阿什莉  -我叫迪倫
- That's Ashley. - I'm Dillon.
-是想問問招聘的事  -定了  就你了
- I was wondering about the job. - Done. Yours.
你找到姑娘了嗎
Did you find a girl yet?
-還沒有  -太可惜了
- Not yet. - That's a shame.
"我叫瑪拉  我是他的奴隸
"My name is Mara and I was his slave.
"我知道我的性解放
"My road to sexual freedom
"只能通過我的服從實現"
could only be found through my submission."
轉過去
Turn around.
別看我
Don't look at me.
"要是他用來綁我的繩子突然斷掉
"Should these ropes he used to tie me down suddenly break,
我也不會動
"I would not have moved.
我是他的奴隸
"I was enslaved to him,
把我定在那里的  不是繩子
"And it was neither rope or cuff or belt
手銬或是皮帶"
that kept me there."
眼睛看哪呢
Where are your eyes?
"而是因為我堅定地需要
"It was my unwavering need
感受他的呼吸撫摸我赤裸的肌膚"
to feel his breath against my bare skin."
"我等待著定會來臨的疼痛
"I waited for the pain that I knew would come,
不是因為火焰
"Not from the flame,
而是因為每個男人似乎都會出現的
"But from the inevitable waning of emotion
不可避免的情緒衰退
"That seemed to take hold of every man.
我無力防備..."
I was defenseless and..."
早啊
Good morning.
天吶  你嚇到我了
Oh, my God. You scared me.
那是我的書
That's my book.
抱歉  我就是瀏覽看看
I'm sorry. I was just skimming through it.
你都流口水了
You were drooling.
沒有
No, I wasn't.
我并不喜歡這樣的書
I don't really like books like this.
好吧
Okay.
但如果你改主意了
But if you change your mind,
我周四會請幾個姑娘過來談論它
I'm having some girls over on Thursday night to talk about it.
讀書俱樂部什么的
Book club thing.
知道嗎  聽上去還真挺有意思
You know what? That actually sounds like fun.
好啊  你看我這本吧
Okay. You can have my copy.
反正你似乎把有幾頁都翻舊了
It looks like you wore out the pages a little bit anyway.
《奴隸》  諾蘭·濟慈著
欲
第
一
季
奴
集
二
謝謝
Thank you.
"諾蘭·濟慈描述了一副性虐
"Nolan Keats paints a provocative picture
隱秘世界的撩人畫卷"
of the BDSM underworld."
還給我  還我還我
Give me that. Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
沒想到你私底下是個禽獸
I never took you as a closet freak.
我才不是  而且你不是說
I'm not, and didn't you promise
今后會更專業一些嗎
to be more professional from now on?
我撒謊了
Oh, I lied.
-猜到了  -這到底是什么書
- Of course you did. - So what is this?
我覺得你看上去不像那種喜歡看小黃書的女孩啊
You don't strike me as a girl who likes to read smut.
是迪倫讀書俱樂部的書  不是小黃書
It's for Dillon's book club, and it's not smut.
好吧  "他的龍根一陣抖動"
Oh, okay. "His penis throbbed."
好吧  不要再羞辱我了
Okay, you can stop embarrassing me.
"我要來..."參加這個讀書俱樂部
"I want to cum..." to the book club.
cum本意有射精的意思  此處同音
不行  只準女性參與
Well, you can't. It's for women only.
太可惜了  我還想弄清楚
Oh, too bad. I'd love to find out
為什么女孩子都突然喜歡看小黃書了
why sex books have suddenly become hip with chicks.
這是福音
It's gospel.
這是寫得很爛的小黃文
It's a poorly written smut story.
就因為這本書的作者更加了解女性嗎
Oh, just because the writer has a better understanding of women?
我很了解女性
I have plenty of understanding of women.
好吧  那給我說說迪倫是怎樣的人
Okay, then explain Dillon to me.
那丫頭瘋瘋癲癲的
The chick's crazy.
但你還是跟她睡了
Yet you slept with her.
只要瘋子夠性感  我們照上不誤
Guys don't have a problem banging crazy if crazy is hot enough.
不  她才不瘋呢
Oh, no, she's not crazy.
三個月前
Three months ago,
她在那邊的廁所跟一個陌生人啪啪啪
she fucked a complete stranger in that bathroom over there.
我覺得這就是瘋子
I'd say that's crazy.
什么
What?
她上的是某個家伙的女朋友
Yeah, some guy's girlfriend.
她們倆之前根本沒說過話
Never even spoken to her before.
我覺得我們應該選有工業化特點的
You know, I think that we might need to go industrial.
非常現代  大氣
You know, I mean, it's modern, it's gorgeous.
跟我們的公寓很搭
It would fit really well in our apartment.
-能夠讓我們...  -隨便你想怎么樣
- It would just make... - Whatever you want.
我都可以
I'm cool with anything.
也許我們能裝飾成
Yeah. I mean, maybe we could even go
拋光混凝土那樣
for some kind of polished concrete look.
弄點抽象藝術
You know, maybe get some abstract art.
我很喜歡那些柱子
You know, I love those columns,
還喜歡頭頂的那些光束
and I love the beams overhead.
然后我們可以搞幾個大沙發墊
Oh, and then we could get some really big sofa cushions,
既舒服  又實用
and then it would be more functional comfort,
而不是搞得很花哨
you know, instead of being actually showy.
不過  我挺喜歡花哨的
Although, I do like to be showy.
也許我們可以弄點大型綠色盆栽
Maybe we could get some big, green, leafy plants, you know?
但是然后我們要用金屬立燈還是交通式燈呢
Oh, but then do we do big metal lamps or do we do track lighting?
我感覺那樣現代風太重了
'Cause I feel that's too modern.
我們要更都市風一些  不是現代風
We need to be a bit more urban, not modern.
我去趟洗手間  很快就回來
I got to go to the bathroom. I'll be right back.
好  去吧
Okay. All right.
都市風  就是這種風格  相信我沒錯的
Urban. That's the way to go. I'm telling you.
把門鎖上
Lock the door.
什么東西
What that?
來  脫掉
Here, take this off.
別出聲
Shut up.
好爽
Yes.
我的天
Oh, my God.
別誤解我意思
Don't get me wrong.
隨意打炮沒什么不對
There's nothing wrong with casual sex.
隨意打炮太他媽爽了  但迪倫比較怪異
Casual sex is fucking great, but Dillon's weird.
怎么  因為她跟你一樣放浪不羈隨心所欲嗎
Why, because she's as emotionally unavailable as you are?
差不多吧
Pretty much, yeah.
我也說不好  我覺得一個女人
I don't know. I think it's kind of cool
能那么隨性恣意還是挺酷的
that a woman can be that spontaneous.
也許你哪天應該來一發試試
Oh. Well, maybe you should try it sometime.
誰不想那樣被上啊
Who wouldn't want to get nailed like that?
我就不想  那是典型的虐待
I wouldn't. It was textbook abuse.
才不是呢
It was not.
瑪拉很明顯是斯德哥爾摩綜合癥的受害者
Mara was clearly a victim of Stockholm syndrome.
好吧  你這就走極端了
Oh, okay, that's extreme.
那完全是強迫性交
It was full on coercion.
他處在強權地位
He was in a position of power.
誰在乎是不是強權地位
Who cares if it was a position of power?
金姆  他用馬鞭抽奧利維亞
Kim, he used a riding crop on Olivia
好像她是種動物一樣
like she was some kind of animal.
好吧  是稍微有點變態
Okay, so it's kinky...
他還用狗鏈到處遛另外一個人
And he yanked that other one around with a leash.
給我舔
Suck it.
別激動  那只是角色扮演
Calm down. It was just role-play.
那不只是角色扮演
It was not just role-play.
他強行奴役他們
He forced them into actual slavery.
而她們還對他意淫得停不下來
And yet they couldn't stop fantasizing about him.
她們當然停不下來  因為書是一個男人寫的
Of course they couldn't, because it was written by a man.
據說而已
So they say.
別告訴我你相信
Please don't tell me you are buying into
"書是一個女人寫的"這種鬼話
that "It was written by a woman" bullshit.
可能就是女人寫的啊
Well, maybe it was.
如果是女人寫的
So if a woman wrote it,
那貶低女性就無關緊要了  對嗎
then we should be completely okay with misogyny, right?
不  這與貶低女性無關
No, that has nothing to do with it.
當然有關系
That has everything to do with it.
社會想讓我們認為
Society wants us to believe
女人是一種可悲的生物
that women are like these pathetic little creatures
生死全然取決于男人的心情
that live and die by a man's happiness.
女人想服從一個男人怎么就可悲了
Why is it pathetic if a woman wants to submit to a man?
你認真的嗎
Are you serious?
一點都不可悲
It isn't pathetic,
更多女人應該嘗試一下
and more women should give it a try.
我只是說在臥室里
I'm just saying that it's fun
放棄一點控制權會別有樂趣  僅此而已
to give up a little control in the bedroom, that's all.
姐們  說話不要說一半好嗎
Dude, you can't just say that and not elaborate.
不要了  我們是來討論這本書的
No. We're here to talk about the book.
書是關于性愛的
Which is about sex,
你不跟我們說的也是關于性愛的  所以
and so is whatever you're not telling us, so...
好吧  你們好煩人
Oh, you're all so annoying.
事件涉及到我丈夫安東尼
Okay, so it involves my husband Anthony
還有他最好的朋友
and his best friend.
已經大愛了
Love it already.
安東尼已經意淫這個好多年了
Yeah. So for years, Anthony had this fantasy.
過來
Get over here.
喜歡嗎
You like that?
姐們  太瘋狂了
Dude, that's fucking crazy.
我知道
I know.
你還樂在其中嗎
And you enjoyed it?
怎么可能不
How could she not?
那都不是她想象的  是她丈夫
It wasn't even her fantasy. It was her husband's.
誰管這個   反正很好玩
Who cares? It was fun.
你是在妄想
You are delusional.
反正沒人可以控制我做什么
Well, no man is going to control what I do
或者我上誰
or who I fuck.
有時候失去控制權有其自身的力量
Sometimes losing control has its own kind of power.
還有多久退給我押金  文森特
諾蘭·濟慈
來看看
Okay.
讓人難以捉摸的諾蘭·濟慈
"諾蘭·濟慈的身份目前無人知曉
"The current identity of Nolan Keats is unknown.
"很多人懷疑作者其實是女性
Many have suspected that the writer is actually a woman
"以筆名來寫作
working under a pen name.
"濟慈的對外事務代理人最近宣布
Keats' literary agent recently announced
"《奴隸》不會有簽名售書活動
that there will be no book tour for "Slave",
"使大家對他/她的身份更加懷疑了"
further fueling suspicions about his or her identity."
我正在你床上滾來滾去
I'm rolling around in your bed right now
這樣我就能聞到你的氣息
so I can smell you.
我就是這么想你
That's how bad it's gotten.
話說你們談過了嗎
So have you had the conversation yet?
好吧  那什么時候
Okay, then when?
你知道我在你床上躺著而你卻
Do you know how hard it is to be here in your bed
在一個鳥不拉屎的地方讓我多煎熬嗎
when you're motocrossing all the way in Fuckit?
誰知道...無所謂了
Who gets... whatever.
我怎么可能知道
How am I supposed to know
怎么讀一個遠在天邊的地方的名字
how to pronounce a place halfway across the world?
糟了  我室友打來的  別掛
Oh, shit. That's my roommate. Hang on.
怎么了
What up?
迪倫把戴著手銬和眼罩的切爾茜推車里了
Dillon just put Chelsea in her car handcuffed and blindfolded.
然后呢
Okay.
Okay?
你難道不覺得有點奇怪嗎
So you don't think that's a little bizarre?
大姐  那是迪倫  我說過她喜歡變態的東西
Dude, it's Dillon. I told you, she's into some freaky shit.
但是她到底在干什么
But what was she doing?
誰知道  誰管它
Who knows? Who cares?
我現在在處理真正的危機呢
I'm dealing with an actual crisis right now.
怎么了  發生什么事了
Why? What happened?
茱爾絲
Jules?
你還在嗎
Are you still there?
好吧你有事要掛了
Of course you have to go.
你總是有事
You always have to go.
我只能在這獨自一人聞你的床單
And I'm just here alone smelling your sheets
亂劍穿身
impaled by a bunch of swords.
只是打個比方
It's a metaphor.
等你回來你一定要去跟她說
So when you get back, you have to have the talk.
沒有你的我會枯萎的
I'm slowly dying here without you.
天啊  你能來我實在是太高興了
Oh, my God. I am so glad you're here.
我跟你說過她很瘋吧
Yeah, well, told you she was crazy.
給我個合理的理由  為什么會有人那樣
Give me one logical reason why somebody would do that?
迪倫這個人毫無理性  所以我給不了你理由
Dillon's not a logical person, so I can't.
不過那姑娘不會出什么事的  對吧
But, I mean, that girl's going to be okay, right?
當然不會
Yeah, of course.
你知道你是在胡思亂想嗎
Do you realize how crazy you sound?
沒有
No.
好吧  你需要再來一瓶啤酒
Okay, you need another beer.
好吧  你可以盡管取笑我
Okay, you can make fun of me all you want,
但是濟慈筆下的男人是女人真正想要的男人
but Keats writes men that women actually want.
好像霸道這種藝術形式不復存在了
It's like aggression is this lost art form.
男人都變成了非常被動消極的小男孩
Men have become these like passive little boys.
是嗎
Oh, have they?
-是的  -好吧
- Yes. - All right.
女人想要的男人是那種
Women just want a guy who can, you know, like,
直接推倒你開干的  知道嗎
throw down and get dirty, you know?
不不不  不不不
No, no, no. No, no, no.
-不行  -怎么了
- No. - What?
我們不能這樣
We are not doing this.
為什么
Why not?
因為我喝醉了
Because I'm drunk.
你也有點醉了
And you're kind of drunk.
-是  -不行
- Yeah. - No.
不行
No.
過來  別想跑
Wait. Where are you going?
好棒
Nice.
謝謝
Thanks.
我明天會后悔嗎
Am I going to regret this tomorrow?
沒人跟你說話  你就一句都不許說
Not a word until you're spoken to.
好了
There you go.
太緊了嗎
Is that too tight?
我喜歡緊一點
I like it tight.
向前坐
Sit forward.
好了
There you go.
迪倫
Dillon?
我說過我會找到一個
I told you I'd find one.
你覺得如何
What do you think?
她很漂亮
She's pretty.
切爾茜  這位是艾略特
Chelsea, I'd like you to meet Elliott.
你好
Hi.
我們開始吧
Let's begin.